import { Question } from "../App";

export const bbData: Question[] =
    [
        {
            "question": "What is Walter White's alias?",
            "options": ["Heisenberg", "Gus", "Saul", "Hank"],
            "answer": "Heisenberg"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was Walter Whiteâ€™s first partner in the meth business?",
            "options": ["Jesse Pinkman", "Gus Fring", "Mike Ehrmantraut", "Tuco Salamanca"],
            "answer": "Jesse Pinkman"
        },
        {
            "question": "What type of car does Walter White primarily drive?",
            "options": ["Pontiac Aztek", "Dodge Charger", "Chevrolet Monte Carlo", "Toyota Tercel"],
            "answer": "Pontiac Aztek"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of Saul Goodman's bodyguard?",
            "options": ["Huell", "Kuby", "Mike", "Todd"],
            "answer": "Huell"
        },
        {
            "question": "What does the acronym 'ABQ' stand for in the show?",
            "options": ["Albuquerque", "American BBQ", "Alaska Business Quarter", "Arizona Bank"],
            "answer": "Albuquerque"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is the owner of Los Pollos Hermanos?",
            "options": ["Gus Fring", "Tuco Salamanca", "Lydia Rodarte-Quayle", "Hector Salamanca"],
            "answer": "Gus Fring"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of the DEA agent who is Walter White's brother-in-law?",
            "options": ["Hank Schrader", "Steve Gomez", "Mike Ehrmantraut", "Gale Boetticher"],
            "answer": "Hank Schrader"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the blue meth's purity percentage that Walter White produces?",
            "options": ["99.1%", "95%", "90%", "80%"],
            "answer": "99.1%"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who kills Gale Boetticher?",
            "options": ["Jesse Pinkman", "Walter White", "Gus Fring", "Hank Schrader"],
            "answer": "Jesse Pinkman"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of the car wash that Walter White buys?",
            "options": ["A1A Car Wash", "Sunshine Car Wash", "Crystal Clean Car Wash", "White's Car Wash"],
            "answer": "A1A Car Wash"
        },
        {
            "question": "What object does Walter use to kill Krazy-8?",
            "options": ["A bike lock", "A gun", "A knife", "Poison"],
            "answer": "A bike lock"
        },
        {
            "question": "What chemical element does Walter White use to start a fire in 'Crazy Handful of Nothin'?",
            "options": ["Mercury", "Magnesium", "Phosphorus", "Lithium"],
            "answer": "Phosphorus"
        }
    ];